well then the next movie was the
brothers yes with yourself moris
Chestnut my man DL hugley Shamar Moore
Tamila Jones Gabriel
Union uh that that was a hit man a $6
million budget 28 million at the box
office plus all the the streaming money
that it's made from the reruns and
everything else like that yeah yeah it
was definitely a hit movie for us um
Jennifer Lewis played her mom and no no
no she played uh Morris's mom she was
one of the moms in it Pal's in it CLI
and pal yep was uh Morris's Nemesis his
stepdad AKA Nemesis um that movie was
really really fun to play
because that was close to me and my boys
you know um and basically I was the
voice of all the guys I was the guy of
reason I was the most vocal guy I was
the guy with the poem I was likey Bros
Over Hoes kind of guy you know what I'm
saying we can't break up our crew
because you want to get married man come
on why you doing this like I was
that guy and um sometime the antagonist
as well but I thought I thought I really
did a great job in that movie of
blending um uh drama and comedy like you
know that's the thing that I feel like I
do pretty well like I'm able to make
real stuff real and funny stuff funny or
you were on season 3 of insecure mhm and
Amanda seals was on the show as well
recently she did an interview with
Shannon
sharp where she talked about how isay
never had her back and and so forth um
she also claimed she was autistic but
then later she said she wasn't
actually she never went to a doctor to
confirm it because she didn't want to
pay 10,000 for the test so it's a little
weird oh I don't mean to La
that's she didn't want P so it was a
self diagnosed autism I guess which is
which is a little different yeah you
know and and you have like I me and
Amanda go back right yeah I be I've
interviewed Amanda I love Amanda I inter
interviewed her on my podcast yeah we're
kind of the same smart man she smart
girl she's sharp she's very honest girl
yeah we came up together I was doing you
know when I was a DJ she was still doing
her thing when you look at people like
Amanda that feel like they've been
blacklisted or they haven't been given
the opportunities they feel they deserve
right and a lot of people in Hollywood
feel this way do you feel that's a fair
assessment or is it just listen there's
only only so many slots not everyone's
going to make it no I think I think what
I love most about Amanda is her honesty
you know what I mean she's super smart
no people don't give her credit for like
she she does her homework she's very
very um honest about stuff and she's
she's so vocal though like I think
that's the thing that's tough is cuz
when you're honest like she is and you
you you standing on business when it
comes to certain topics and things you
really passionate about people it's like
Hot Grits to people woo damn you know
what I mean and this is
uh the land of comments you know people
feel like they could just talk about
your situation people got something to
say everybody's a comedian online so if
you toss some up you better hope
you comfortable with it cuz it's going
to be a million that got
to say X Y and Z and you ain't this and
you ain't or who the are you you
ain't autistic you know like it's so
many ds so for for me I just think it's
tough for women in general you know you
know this business comedy is a male
dominated sport you know the business is
you know Hollywood is tough on girls you
know what I'm saying if you if you don't
fit the mold if you just not if you
ain't fine as hell or you got to be
skinny enough or if you going to be big
you got to be the right kind of big like
this so it's so many things that women
did with that guys never think about
it's like for a woman to make it
successfully in the entertainment
business and keep her sanity and her
success is I think it's tough well yeah
I just had Michael J white and his wife
Gillian white on my show and we talked
about how in one of her early early
roles they wanted her to be naked like
topless and she she didn't want to do it
and they were like if you don't do this
you're going to be blacklisted your
whole career is over and you know this
is her first role she's like I think in
her early 20s she doesn't understand
whether this is true or not but she's
freaking out you know and I'm like well
isn't that the document you know when
you sign she's like probably but I don't
know any better like I don't know what I
signed I just trying to be in a movie
and you know it is it is a tough
environment it is and ultimately the
director said okay it's fine you don't
have to be topless it's cool and she was
still in the movie but all right you
know but this type of stuff you've seen
this kind of thing thing you know happen
yo in Hollywood man here's the thing
that people won't won't really talk
about man there's a lot of concessions
to things that you may do or not right
you know I mean you got to be able to
stand on your own you know what I mean
it's like I'm I'm my whole my rule for
my whole career is like yo bro I ain't
come out here to play myself you know
what I'm saying I came out here to get
on came out here to be an example of
success I feel like I would never want
to do anything that would embarrass
myself or my family like if I can't go
home to the regular barber shop where I
get my haircut and and and my boys who
grew up with me be like yo B man what
the you do that for well you
you talked about how you've been offered
roles where you'd wear a dress yeah like
all kinds of what what movie was
this oh God there's so many of these
little quirky things I don't want to
step on a grenade but I just want to say
certain things I just ain't doing it
ain't me it ain't my okay so you turned
down a dress roll what else I just
turned down RS that wasn't fitting to me
like I'm uncomfortable with that Ro like
that's not what I want to do like that
my You' been offered gay rolls for
example yeah there's there's plenty of
them out there they need they need uh
they need actors so but you've turned
down gay roles I turned down roles that
I that I that's not me yeah yeah it's
like that's not I mean it's not that
it's a gay role I mean there's roles
that they need but then I'm like okay
well get somebody that could do that and
kill it like go and bring it
you don't see me getting no Spanish
roles you know what I'm saying like I'm
cool I I think what people need to do is
be comfortable with whatever it is and
do the best at that but here's the thing
whatever you do you got to live with it
yeah you know what I mean if a woman is
in a movie and they asking her to do a
real really sexual scene and she's
uncomfortable she needs to say that or
say I want I see it this way but some
time when you knew you don't know that
you can have an opinion about it you
don't know
that you know your take could be better
than theirs I remember I interviewed uh
DeAndre Bond and uh he did a rape scene
where I believe he got raped lock down
and he said that that's tough he didn't
want to do it the director kind of
convinced him to do it he said he went
into his dressing room and cried after
that scene yeah man because what people
people don't realize too about
acting there has you give a piece of
yourself away in these scenes that you
do right you got to find some truth in
this scene for you so that you're able
to do it right okay if you got to do a
heavy heartbreaking scene you're going
to have to grab something from your life
that you know that broke your heart and
grab that emotion and and those words
are coming from that pain right soon as
they say cut that ain't up off you
bro you know what I mean you basically
done dug up some that you got to do
this monologue in and you got to do it
like eight times so it's it brings up a
bunch of for you you might do the
best performance ever but people that
watch the movie going to say oh my God
you were
amazing wow oh my God you made me cry
you you that happened to me
they don't know like what you had to dig
up to get it that's why a lot of times
like when people talk about Heath Ledger
playing The Joker do you understand how
dark that character was bro like real
actors know bro like Heath went
somewhere that you scared to go in there
bro you he walked past that door went
down the hall and went down in the
basement and then turned and went down
another level to grab all the levels of
the
Joker and how do you get up out that
basement yeah I mean he died short
shortly after yeah you see what I'm
saying yeah so as an
actor to be quite honest you just got to
be able to walk with yourself no matter
what role you get offered and can you
bring the best of yourself in that r